[Oasis]
[This drama is fiction. The characters, places, agencies, organizations, incidents, and settings have no relevance to real-life events.]
[Episode 3]
Aunt, Uncle!
You'd better not forget your promise.
Of course! Don't worry.
That's right.
We moved our office, Jung Shin. Okay?
Stop by when you come to Seoul.
I will treat you to Chinese food, your favorite.
Honey.
Isn't everything working out too well for us these days?
I'm getting a bit scared
that we might become chaebol.
Don't get scared!
Don't you remember what that fortune teller at Miari said?
Around this time, there will be a big change in our lives.
Oh, goodness!
[Jung Guk Young]
Hey, Ms. Oh!
Give me some alcohol, Yang Ja.
Did you fight again with your aunt?
Should I introduce you to some rich old man?
So you could keep your theater?
You don't have a rich young man?
Would young men look for you?
They would look for me.
Yeah, right!
You said that you had an aunt who runs a theater in Gwangju, right?
Yeah, my mom's cousin.
What's her name?
Aunt Geum Ok. Cha Geum Ok.
I heard my aunt is the only woman in the movie promotion industry in our country.
Even my mom and dad can't do anything in front of her.
What's the deal with this little girl?
Who are you, Ahjumma?
If you don't want to get hurt, stay out of this.
Oh, you're the daughter of Namhae Theater's Mr. Oh?
But how do you know my aunt?
The Commander,
I mean, the Deputy Director
was worried a lot about
whether you had any difficulties while moving.
I see.
But what do you mean by "Deputy Director"?
I heard he was leaving the military.
Did he already move somewhere else?
Oh, yes. He went to Namsan.
If it's Namsan,
then isn't that a major promotion?
We've already prepared a place for you to stay in Seoul.
If you have anything else you need, let me know.
No, thank you so much.
Do you...
have something you're worried about?
No.
I left a message for my son in Seoul,
and I was wondering if he would come.
Wouldn't he come since his mother is moving to Seoul?
He would, right?
How is it? Do you like it?
Yes.
Thanks to you, I was able to get such a nice house for less than the market price.
Thank you so much.
I guess Cheol Woong hasn't come yet?
He said he would stay at his own place for the time being.
His school is a bit far from here.
I was going to properly introduce him to you, Oppa.
I'm sure I'll get to meet him soon.
But more importantly, shouldn't you also get a job, Yeo Jin?
It would be a shame to let your degree at a prestigious university go to waste.
That was such a long time ago.
I happen to have a job I want to recommend to you.
Do you want to hear about it?
Hey, you, wake up!
I said wake up!
What are you doing on a morning like this?
In front of the sacred theater!
You must have taken an early morning train.
To pay the balance already?
O-Oh... well, not really...
Ma'am, how about a daytime drink...
I mean...
how about having a hangover drink with me?
This is...
a cognac that I worked hard to obtain.
Do you think there will be a pub that opens in the morning?
There's no need to go far.
You're telling me to buy Namhae Theater?
Yes.
I owe the bank about 70 million won,
and there are some other debts.
Please buy the theater with those debts included.
If I pay off your debt,
are you saying you will sell the theater for cheap?
Yes.
Why?
Although I couldn't keep my promise,
you trusted me.
Also,
I feel like if I said I would buy the theater back later,
you would be someone who'd return it to me.
This young girl
is talking like all she ate was conniving snakes for food.
I don't do business that comes at a loss for me.
In "The Godfather,"
Vito Corleone says this line.
"I'm gonna make him
an offer he can't refuse."
Honestly, the theater is just a sweetener.
I'm the real deal.
I will sell myself to you, Ma'am.
Whoa, you're a tough cookie, aren't you?
What are you worth?
I know you are not satisfied with being an entertainment promoter just in Jeolla-do.
You should become a promoter who dominates the entire country.
I will help you with that.
Hey,
it does seem like
you watched a lot of movies.
Since you made your offer like in the movies,
I will respond to you very realistically.
Get lost.
Thanks for the drink.
W-Wait...
Ma'am!
I refused an offer that I couldn't refuse.
So you have more to say to me?
I'm sorry.
About what?
I was arrogant.
You can make the offer. I will do whatever it is.
Oh, really?
Then, for me,
I will make you an offer that you can refuse. Okay?
But...
you should hear my offer on your knees.
Here?
You can refuse.
Please tell me.
First,
I will pay off your debt and take over your theater.
When the right time comes.
Second,
you will work under me
as a maid.
I said you can refuse.
I'll do it!
♫ Look at me! Look at me! Look at me! ♫
♫ Like the flowers in the winter solstice of December, look at me! ♫
M-Mom...
Come out.
I heard you haven't been to the boarding home for the past few days.
And you didn't visit me when I moved to Seoul, either.
I'm sorry.
If you've done that much, you've done enough.
You even got dragged into military service.
Stop with the protests
and study for the bar exam.
You say the same thing that Doo Hak hyung said to me.
You met Doo Hak?
Yes.
How is he doing?
I don't know.
It just seems like he's changed a bit.
Don't meet Doo Hak again in the future.
Nothing good will come out of being connected with him.
Aren't we...
already connected?
And really inextricably at that?
Cheol Woong.
Please go home now.
I will come visit soon.
Don't talk like an idiot.
You are not connected to Doo Hak in any way!
He is a convicted criminal who committed murder, and you're...
- a college student with a bright future, got that?
- Why are you being like that?
Mom.
Heaven and earth know,
and you and I know it.
Do you...
really want to see your mom die?
Cheol Woong.
Who do you think
I'm living for, huh?
I mean, why are we still here like this?
Aigoo, do you think it's that easy to find a sucker?
The timing is important.
If we take longer, we need to give up on this!
Just wait a bit longer.
Aigoo, this is almost a done deal...
So you should've found a sucker before we got to this point, Hyungnim!
Gosh, look at what we're doing. This is doomed!
Oh, Hyungnim.
Here.
Who is this?
Well,
it's a villain. A bad guy.
It doesn't matter if he's a villain or an angel.
Does he have some money?
He's got a lot.
The greedier the guy, the easier they fall for our trap.
[Jung Guk Young]
[Building Information in the Certificate of Registration]
[Certificate of Registration]
I really like the building,
but this is too expensive, especially since we have to pay it all upfront.
How about you lower the price a bit?
Gosh...
This is expensive?
I'm selling this in a rush at an unbelievable price
of 50% of its value because I'm going to America!
But does it make any sense that you want me to lower the price?
You're just trying to rip me off, aren't you?
Oh, my God!
Boss,
- please cancel this business arrangement.
- Cancel?
- Ma'am!
- What does cancel mean?
Wait.
Give them just a little bit of time to think.
- Just a moment.
- What the heck are you doing?
What does "Cancel, please" mean?
- Cancel, please?
- I don't know, either.
Oh, yes.
Here.
Gosh, okay. Fine!
Let's sign the contract.
Aigoo, Ma'am!
You've made the right choice!
You're going to become rich!
But...
I'm short on a little bit of cash
even after getting all the loans I can get,
so would it be okay for us to pay for part of it with this instead?
[Certificate of Registration: Namhae Theater]
The evaluated price of this is at least 120 million won,
and you can get at least 50 million won after paying off the included 70 million won in bank debt,
but I'll value it as 30 million won and give it to you.
W-What is this?
It's Namhae Theater in Yeosu.
[Certificate of Registration: Namhae Theater]
The business is profitable,
and it's the top theater in Yeosu.
Why don't you believe me? Ask anyone in Yeosu!
For this price, you would be getting this for almost nothing.
We're pretty much giving it away to you.
Well...
we don't usually take property for payment...
But since you're in a rush, you should take their offer.
I'll make sure to get it liquidated quickly for you.
Then you have to take responsibility for it if anything happens!
Oh, of course!
All right, let's sign the contract.
Yes. Honey, the money.
I'll count the cash, okay?
Gosh, there's no need for that.
Here.
And here.
- The bag was a bit small...
- It was a bit small...
Yes, yes, yes...
Okay.
All right, that's it!
Oh, my gosh!
- Here, take it!
- How long has it been!
[CEO Go Poong Ho]
What should we do with this?
I accepted it because I thought they might suspect us,
but that woman was lying. As for this theater...
100 million won? It probably isn't even worth 20 or 30 million won.
Hyungnim, something like that is a headache!
If you try to liquidate that, it takes a long time, and your identity will be exposed.
Just give it to me.
Yeah!
G-Give it to him for introducing the sucker.
Yeah, that sounds like a great idea.
Typically, a new recruit doesn't get any shares,
but since we earned a pretty good profit this time, be generous.
All right. Aigoo...
Here. That's all right with you, right?
- I'm happy with this.
- Okay, okay.
Then, we are all going to go our separate ways, okay?
I'll call you guys when I get more business later,
so you guys all watch yourselves, okay?
[Certificate of Registration: Namhae Theater]
You also stay well, okay?
All right, time to go.
We should hurry out! Hurry! Hurry!
What is he planning on doing with that?
Stop chit-chatting and messing around! Hurry!
Oh, my.
We went in the wrong direction.
Let's go.
- Oh, my!
- Poong Ho hyungnim.
It's been a while.
W-What brings you guys here?
The rumors are all over
about how you managed to pull the rug under someone pretty good.
Gosh.
Who said such nonsense?
Noonim, you said to me yesterday in the motel
that something good might happen soon and that we should run away together!
Hey! That's because you kept asking me for money yesterday!
Gosh! Seriously!
Geez, that trap of yours! Why would you tell that gigolo...
Go, go, go.
Hey, let go!
No, you can't! You can't! You can't!
Geez!
Whoa!
Wow!
Oh, okay, okay.
Let's split the money among ourselves.
How about 7 to 3?
We'll take 7, and you guys take 3.
- How about it?
- That's funny.
W-Well then,
how about 5 to 5?
Gosh.
Okay, then we'll be cool about it,
and do 7 to 3.
We'll take...
3, how about it?
Hyungnim, just go somewhere and have pork belly and soju.
- And piss off.
- Aigoo, seriously...
There was one more guy.
Hey. Come over here.
- Me?
- Punk...
Punk...
You're one of them, right?
Not anymore.
We decided to go our own way. Isn't that right?
Give me what you got, too.
What do you mean?
Geez, this is tiring.
This guy's got nothing.
This is it?
Hyungnim, isn't he part of your family?
Gosh...
what do you mean by part of my family?
H-He's just a probationary employee.
I'll see you again next time.
Wait.
Is this guy crazy?
I don't care about the money, but you should give me that.
There's an owner for that.
Hey, kiddo.
The owner you're speaking of...
is me.
It's me. Ass–
Whoa, whoa!
Right there!
I told you there's a separate owner for this.
I'm leaving. Bye.
Where are you going by yourself?
- We should go together.
- Hey, hey, hey!
Oh, my, the money.
You bastards eat two to three times
more than what others eat
and yet you got beaten up by one guy?
Get in the pushup position.
Get in position!
Enough.
No, Hyungnim. These guys need to be disciplined the military way.
[CEO Yeom Kwang Tak]
Okay.
I mean, they were in and out of jail from their youth
so none of them went to military service.
So, why are you disciplining them in military style?
Get up.
Get out, you bastards.
Did you tell them to do it?
Excuse me?
Oh, yes.
I heard that Go Poong Ho finished a job...
I couldn't tell you in advance because you were away.
You first take on a job and then report to me after?
Right. The action leader should have quick judgment like that, right?
You did well.
T-Thank you.
But the results weren't good.
I'm sorry, Hyungnim.
No, it's all right.
Which one would you like? Pick one.
Excuse me?
What are you doing not choosing one?
I'm sorry, Hyungnim. I'll make sure nothing like this ever happens again.
Yeah, right, asshole. Come here.
Put your head here, you asshole.
This one's for the bad result, man.
Got it?
And is Go Poong Ho your friend?
He's also a hyung to me, you rude bastard.
This bastard... You...
Bring Poong Ho to me in three days.
Also, bring that bastard who beat up our guys.
Got it?
Yes, Hyungnim.
Get out, you bastard.
Oh, gosh, I'm dying.
Aigoo.
Are we still not there yet?
We're almost there.
Gosh, more stairs! Really?
Geez!
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
You should have gotten a room where it's a bit flatter!
If you didn't have money, you should have said something.
If you did, I would have lent you some money– Aigoo!
How can I borrow money from you when we're not even family?
Aigoo. Do you have rice?
I just usually eat ramen.
And on weekends, I eat food that the church charity organization provides.
Sometimes, I eat while working manual labor.
Gosh, that's why I said we should buy some rice before we come!
Yeah, Hyungnim!
More importantly, Kwang Tak and his guys
must be so spiteful right now.
I know!
Once he flips out, he doesn't stop at anything.
Gosh, and that No. 2 guy. Geez, he's just...
And that sucker would have found out by now that they've been had.
- Come on, Ahjussi. Take a look at this.
- Geez, come on!
[Seongjin Constructions]
It has my name, Oh Tae Ja, written on it!
Your wife definitely said you were going to America and–
What are you guys talking about!
My wife died a long time ago!
She died?
- Why did she die?
- No way!
There's no way!
No! Ahjussi, yours is fake, right?
Ahjussi, yours is fake, right?
[Certificate of Registration]
It's exactly the same!
Give me a break.
Yours is fake.
This one is the real one.
From the looks of it, you guys must have been defrauded. Come to your senses,
and hurry over to the police station!
Oh, no...
What police station!
Oh, no! There's no way this is true!
- Gosh! Honey!
- Oh, Honey!
What do we do now?
Since we're going to be chased by Kwang Tak and the police...
What now?
Hey, now's not the time to be yawning!
If you beat up Kwang Tak's guys like that,
you should take responsibility for the consequences!
Gosh, then just give the money to them. That would take care of it.
With what clues are the police going to catch us anyway?
So, just give them the money,
and you won't have any problems.
Gosh, b-but still...
You said we should all go our separate ways.
That was just Mr. Go saying stuff.
You said I don't get any shares because I'm a newbie.
- Aigoo.
- Seriously!
Everyone, return to your homes.
I have to work manual labor early in the morning, so I'm going in to rest.
Hey, okay!
Okay, okay. I was wrong.
From now, let's be a family.
Yeah, okay. A family!
Yeah, from now, we can give him a share in the profits!
Are you really going to accept me as your family?
Of course!
And you all will become my family?
- Oh, of course!
- Don't even mention it!
No, no.
You will become our boss from now on!
Boss!
Aigoo.
Now we are a family!
A family!
Hurry up and leave.
Okay, we'll be on our way.
Go inside!
Family!
Go on your way.
Now we are a family!
Oh, young tenant.
Is today a special day?
You have family inside.
Go on ahead inside.
Yeah.
Oppa!
Why didn't you come home
or call us?
Do you know how worried Mom was?
Stop talking
and let's just eat.
Do you know how much
- Mom cried after you called her?
- This girl...
Hey, girl,
who do you think you are that you're eating the drumstick?
Gosh, all I ate today was one bowl of noodles!
I'm so starving that my belly button is about to stick to my back.
Mom, you should eat up, too.
Gosh, it hasn't been that long since you came out of prison,
but seeing how handsome you look...
It's like you're a Seoul person.
Really?
- Oh, right.
- Oppa, I ended up working at a factory in Seoul.
Gil Ja unni says
it's Bangil Industrial Company in Guro-dong,
where they make zippers and razors.
Then what about school?
Oppa, you know, too, right?
I wasn't on your level,
but I was at least in the top five in my class.
But these girls who are worse at studying than me are all going to high school,
but Father kept telling me to quit school and work at a factory...
I was so angry!
Shut your mouth.
Do you know why I said I would go to the factory without making a fuss?
So that I can go back to school by earning my own money!
You just watch.
I will go all the way to college.
Stop rambling
and just eat.
Stuff yourself. Okay?
Red light, green light. One, two, three!
You resented your father a lot, right?
I resented him a lot, too.
I thought how heartless your father was, not visiting his son in prison once.
If you're going to talk about Father, just stop.
When you turned 20 and transferred to Gwangju,
that was the day before Chuseok*.
(Harvest Day in Korea, holiday similar to Thanksgiving)
But out of the blue, your father said he'll go to a cousin's house in Gwangyang to offer ancestral rites.
I didn't want to bother with preparing food for the ancestral rites, so I told him to go ahead.
Mom.
Just hurry inside and go to bed.
You don't want to hear it?
Yes.
Still, listen.
But after telling me he would return around Chuseok evening,
he didn't return even when it became the day after Chuseok.
I wondered if something had happened, so I called his cousin in Gwangyang,
and he said, "What are you talking about?"
He said your father never came.
I was so scared.
I couldn't sleep at all
and couldn't even eat anything.
It was only after two days
after Chuseok had passed, that your father
walked into the house at night.
Aigoo, Doo Hak's father!
Doo Hak's father! Doo Hak's father!
What happened!
Where did you go that you're only returning now?
I thought I would die from being worried about you!
Gosh, just make me some food.
[Yeosu -> Gwangju]
Your father doesn't have any relatives in Gwangju.
So why would he have gone all the way there?
He went to where you were.
I checked when Jung Ok and I went to visit you the following month.
At that time,
your father left money for your detention fund.
So your father
put in all the money he had for his returning bus and food,
and walked all the way from Gwangju to Yeosu
for two days straight.
Don't hate your father too much.
I told you to head on inside and go to bed!
Doo Hak...
Gosh!
Doo Hak!
♫ Oh, oh, our South Korea ♫
Hey!
♫ Oh, oh, our nation ♫
♫ Oh, oh, I'll love it forever ♫
Hey!
Wake up!
Go wash your face!
♫ Oh, oh, our South Korea ♫
[Proper way to use the machine. Check the power supply switch. Check for glitches regularly.]
Unni.
Give me an energy pill.
- Just one, please!
- Gosh, this girl...
Please!
You've already asked me for so many!
I'm so sleepy that I'm going crazy.
What if I can't complete the workload at this rate?
Please...
I won't be responsible even if you collapse from dizziness.
Okay.
Thank you for your hard work.
Come out to our evening class if you have time.
Gil Ja! Hello!
Oh, yes.
Please take a yulmoo tea.
Oh, it's all right.
Come on, I won't ask you to come out to night class, so please take one.
I told you I'm fine.
Please give it to us.
Yes.
Hurry up!
You're Jung Ok, right?
Yes.
There are many people who passed the GED.
[Recruiting Night School Students]
If you study a bit, you'll definitely pass on your first try.
Oh, okay.
But there's something I'd like to ask.
Are you a commie?
S-Sorry?
I heard from Gil Ja unni
that people who go to night school or in labor unions
are all commies...
You're here?
We need to...
draw the bigger picture today.
Well...
the thing is...
I'm not yet...
Get off.
I'll give you one week.
If you don't locate the leadership hideout by then,
your family will receive your death notice.
Do you know what this is?
This is the hard-earned tax money of the people.
So...
let's show some patriotism.
This asshole doesn't understand the situation.
Hey, how dare you protest and sell your country over to the commies
when you come from a family of independence activists?
Throw him into boot camp
and make an example out of him.
Hurry on.
Hey!
Come on! Stop stalling!
Get up there!
Hello?
- Mom.
- Cheol Woong!
Is this Cheol Woong?
It's really you, Cheol Woong?
Yes, Mom.
Cheol Woong!
Where are you?
Did you really join the military on your own?
[Special Enrollment Cases: Army Headquarters]
Don't be like this, Mom.
It just turned out that way. I'm doing well.
Cheol Woong.
Y-You don't need to join the military.
Where are you? I'll go to you.
M-Mom, I don't have time.
The military has changed.
They have good food, and they let me sleep well.
They don't give any more beatings, Mom, so don't worry about me and—
Mom?
Mom...
You really...
miss your mother, right?
I can send you on leave as early as tomorrow.
And I can shorten your military service, too.
Do you want to try...
loving your country?
I...
already love this country.
You know very well that's not what my question means.
I don't really know...
what you mean.
You don't know?
It's simply what I said. "Loving your country."
How do you love your country?
It's catching spies and commies.
If you find and report commies,
we arrest those assholes and boost national security.
Are you...
asking me to be a mole?
What do you mean, mole?
That's what...
we call a patriot.
Loving your country.
This is the frontline.
It's a very dangerous place.
No one will know
even if you disappear.
Choi Cheol Woong.
I'm giving you an  opportunity right now.
Don't you need to continue your patriotic family lineage?
I don't want to.
Write it.
Hey, put him through one more run.
I'll write it! I will!
I'll write it...
- Hey, Hyung!
- What happened!
- What's this?
- How?
What the heck?
- What happened?
- You didn't get hurt? Are you okay?
Come on!
♫ The life running... ♫
Right now is the time to make our stand.
Yes, right now is the time.
I said we couldn't. Everyone got arrested.
When will it be if not now?
Hyung!
Why did you come back here? It's dangerous!
You're here?
I'm sorry for making you all suffer.
We worried so much because of the cops.
- Please take a seat.
- Thank you.
Let's sit.
By the way, what brings you here?
I need to at least see your faces before I go.
Are you okay?
Have some of this, too.
Where are you headed?
You know him, right?
I know you do!
You!
You sons of bitches!
"After confirming each other's feelings,
Ju Seok gets Black Glove in the taxi.
Ju Seok and Jun Il transport the luggage from the handcart to the taxi.
The three start to get hopeful.
And the screen fades out."
The scenario ends here.
It's a little dark, huh?
Who's the director again?
It's Bae Chang Ho's debuting work.
Kim Bo Yeon, Ahn Sung Ki, and Kim Hee Ra are the main cast.
I see. It's not bad.
By the way, I'm curious about this one thing, Boss.
It'd be faster for you you to read the scenario yourself,
so why do you always tell me to read it to you?
Didn't you know?
I don't know how to read.
What?
You really don't know how to read?
How did you read the ledgers all this time, then?
When did I ever read them?
I just memorize them when my bookkeeper reads them to me.
Whoa, how do you memorize this?
The landlord's apparently head over heels for his wife in Japan,
so he doesn't really stay in Korea.
It's perfect for us to use!
A total of 200 million won...
- for the production cost?
- That's correct, President Cha.
The work has some level of completion,
but it's about the poverty in cities.
So there will be some censorship and correction.
It'll also be Rated-R. No underage viewers.
So will it make money or not?
If I were you...
I wouldn't invest in it.
In that case...
I'll need to invest in it.
Sorry?
- Why?
- Because...
the arrogant smarties are the ones who are always wrong.
Hand him a postdated check for 30 million won.
Dated in a month, okay?
Thank you.
Thank you, President Cha.
Everyone else was reluctant to invest.
You're...
like an army of support by my side.
I'm not trying to help you.
It's because I smell money here.
Sorry?
You smell money?
Whoa...
This building is pretty good.
Since there's info on developments nearby,
we just need to put it up for about 300 million won.
And people will flock like herd dogs.
Whoa, she must be an actress.
She's really pretty.
But who is she?
Boss, do you know her?
Let's leave if you're done looking around.
Just come for a second.
It's because she's really pretty. Come and take a look.
Hurry up. How are you so young and not interested in women?
Go take a look.
For the movie...
I was right, huh? Isn't she pretty?
She's not pretty at all.
Let's hurry up and go, I said!
He took his sweet time looking.
Our boss has high standards, huh?
You can start living here from now.
Wait—
What's this place for?
Oh, my.
You're really as dense as a rock.
Can't you tell from just looking?
It's Namdo Film Studio's Seoul branch.
Gosh.
There was a dimwit whom I fired about two weeks ago.
So, starting today,
you're the employee and the branch manager at the same time.
Why? You're so out of it since you
got promoted too fast, aren't you?
Sweetie,
buy what you need with this.
Boss!
Wait...
you need to tell me what I need to do.
Oh, my. Look at this girl.
How can you be asking me when you
also have run a theater before?
Also, I don't even  know how to read.
And you're a college dropout.
Who'd teach whom?
Aigoo, whatever.
Oh Jung Shin, you're the  crazy wench.
How can you make a living when you have no eyes for people?
Gosh.
What are my eyes good for?
Hello?
Hello.
President Cha?
♫ I want to hold on your hand ♫
You need to speak if you called!
What the heck?
♫ Forever more, the only one ♫
♫ I want to look at your mind, hate me or nice ♫
Gosh!
♫ Beautiful your life ♫
♫ Come over here, back in your love, in my life ♫
Again?
♫ Let me go and my life ♫
Hello.
♫ Let me go ♫
Hello?
♫ And  your life ♫
What the heck is this, seriously?
Hey, you!
You better stop prank-calling!
You're an elementary school student, right?
I guess you don't know what a nasty temper I've got.
If you waste another call,
I'll chase you down to the end of the universe and
break your fingers so you can't dial ever again.
You got that?
You little!
Aigoo!
We're almost done now.
Hey*! Hey, run away!
("Hyung" also means "hey")
- The detectives are coming in. Hurry!
- Gosh...
Hey! Get them all!
Hey!
Stay still!
Hyung, you go first.
Hey, are you okay? Can you move?
I'm okay. You guys go ahead.
Hurry up and go.
I'm okay, so leave me and go!
Stay still!
Get that asshole!
Get him!
It's okay.
Sorry?
He's one of us.
Sir.
Take care.
What's this?
Did you follow me?
Follow you, my ass.
I said you're one of us.
And families protect each other.
Gosh, those fellas aren't part of the leadership.
It's just a regular club!
- Okay?
- Okay, I see.
However...
one of them might know the information I want.
So I'm just raking them all in.
Choi Cheol Woong...
I don't need hundreds of small fish.
I just need one big fish.
Wouldn't that also save you some face as well?
I'm sick of showing you this picture, too.
Let's love your country for once!
Love my country?
Okay.
Please let me love my country. Okay?
Just send me back to the army instead
and stand guard by the barbed wires!
Have you gone mad?
You want to die, huh?
You talk too much.
If you go back to the army...
you can die without anyone knowing.
No one will ever know how you died or why you died, either.
That's what's called death under suspicious circumstances.
You seem to have gotten a little gutsy now that you socialized a bit.
How about it?
Shall I send you back to the army?
I'm telling you this because you're a family.
Always be grateful, you punk.
The place does have a guard,
but he only knows the building manager
and he doesn't know what the landlord looks like!
What?
Whoa, the heavens are helping!
Whoa, isn't this such a good deal?
How much do you think we can get for this?
Still, we always need to be careful.
Even if you think the fire is out,
piss on it just to make sure it's out.
You just watch out for gigolos.
Gosh, seriously.
- Jand Deuk, get the certificate of registration.
- Yes?
Okay!
- What's that?
- What—
Why do you live so high up? Huh?
Gosh...
come out.
Let's have a drink.
Who's that punk?
He's my friend.
Gosh, I almost peed myself thinking he was a cop!
- Seriously.
- Aigoo.
Oh, my...
Come on, seriously.
Let's really just have one more shot.
Hurry up and go to sleep inside, you punk. Also...
if you come over for a drink one more time, you're dead.
If so...
just kill me now, please.
Who beat you up so bad that your ankle is like that?
Oh, this?
It's from loving my country.
Are you fighting for Independence or something?
We're here.
Choi Cheol Woong.
Whoa, you survived somehow, huh?
Shall we have a word separately?
Who the heck are you guys?
If you have something to say, say it here.
I'm Cheol Woong's sunbae.
Don't worry and wait inside.
It'll only take a moment.
I told you to talk here.
O-Okay, okay.
Th-These are...
my closest sunbaes.
Hyung...
you go ahead and rest inside.
I'll be right in.
I'm going to leave, you punk.
O-Okay.
Okay, then. Take care.
Hey, Cheol Woong!
Choi Cheol Woong!
Oh, excuse me. Where's the movie club?
♫ 30 million of our people in the land of Korea ♫
♫ You and I are the ones to save them ♫
♫ Let's go, let's go, let's go to battle ♫
[Your whistle-blowing will save numerous classmates]
Cheol Woong...
let's be honest here.
How many times do I need to tell you?
I'm really not it.
I'm telling you, I'm not a mole.
Then who's the detective who let you go?
And who's the one who talked to you?
That's why I'm saying...
let me talk to the female student who saw it at the dorm.
How is she sure it was me when it was so dark at night?
You were limping, they said!
Who else could it be?
Other friends who were unhurt all got arrested.
But you were the only one who didn't get caught, even with your injury.
- Does this make sense?
- Answer her!
Hyung...
I ran toward the east gate, not the outback.
And I didn't even limp.
I was too nervous and running, so I didn't even know it hurt.
I only realized it hurt after I escaped to safety!
Yes. That's why I drank alcohol!
Don't you all have  an experience like that? No?
- Gosh, seriously...
- Cheol Woong...
We all know you didn't want to...
become a spy.
You were drafted by force when you were exempt from service.
And the sudden early discharge.
I can guess what those bastards did to you.
Since countless classmates were done like that and even died.
So let it all go and confess now.
We're not trying to harm you right now.
We need to let the world know how evil those bastards
can get in order to trample on democratization!
Cheol Woong, I beg of you.
Let's blow the whistle.
Hyung!
♫ Are you going to cower in fear at our enemy's strength? ♫
♫ Are you going to lose hope at our powerlessness? ♫
♫ Where the sword of justice— ♫
You said the talk would only take a little time.
But it must've taken all night.
Where is Cheol Woong?
We had a short talk last night, and I sent him back home.
Gosh, come on now.
I slept alone in Cheol Woong's room until this morning.
Then he must've gone to another drinking buddy.
Hey, wait a minute.
Even educated college students lie, huh?
Cheol Woong's here, isn't he?
He said he wasn't!
Whoa, you're quite the tough guy.
Please go back. They're from UDT and the marines.
Oh, my. How scary.
I'll count to ten. If Cheol Woong doesn't come out by then,
I'll be the seeker. Okay?
Seven...
Eight...
Are you all done hiding?
Nine!
Ten.
I'm going to look for him now, okay?
If you come up here...
we can't help it, either.
Shit!
Hey, it's the cops.
Cheol Woong!
Choi Cheol Woong, are  you here?
It's hard for me to find you if you hide too well!
I wasn't...
going to go this far on students...
but the seeker needs to find everyone for it to end. Right?
Okay.
This little—
- Get him!
- Stop it!
Come out.
I found you.
Leave.
Hey, you punk! I almost died.
Let's go.
Choi Cheol Woong!
- Gosh...
- You've got a great friend.
However...
let's not live in shame.
That's right.
We can't live shamefully.
We can't live embarrassing lives.
But you know...
even in the worst situation, I did my best not to be shameful.
If I were really a mole!
Hyung and all of you, too!
You guys wouldn't be here right now.
Get it?
Hey, let's go. All right?
Let's go.
Why didn't you tell them honestly?
That whistle-blowing thing, you know?
Right...
you need to have a whistle to blow it,
but you don't have a conscience, huh.
Right?
By the way,
why did you come in, even getting beat up like that?
Were you worried something bad might happen to me?
Of course.
I don't care about you getting injured or dying,
but where would I get the payment for the debt you owe me?
Right?
You...
can't die even if you die until you pay me back, you punk.
I'm in for some deep trouble, huh?
But at least one thing's resolved.
You can't...
do the spying work anymore.
What would be your use after all this ruckus?
Is that so?
Oh, my.
Choi Cheol Woong is one luck guy. How fortunate.
Crazy punk.
Hyung.
I...
really didn't sell out any of my friends
who I did demonstrations with.
Even when those bastards...
beat me and threatened me so badly!
But how...
How can they do this to me?
Hey, get on.
Get on my back, you asshole!
Aigoo, shit.
You're so freaking heavy.
Hyung...
don't you want to go down to Yeosu once?
Let's go down, watch a movie, see my dad...
and see your dad, too.
- And meet Jung Shin, too.
- Cut it out.
Why?
You actually want to go, don't you?
You miss Jung Shin, too, right?
Gosh, you go there if you want, you punk!
Hey, this can't do. Get off now.
- W-Wait.
- Get off!
Just up to there.
In that case, shut your trap and
be quiet on the way, okay?
♫ I want to hold on your hand ♫
♫ I want it to be like a birthday ♫
♫ No matter, you will be here, forevermore  ♫
♫ The only one ♫
♫ I want to look at your mind, hate me or nice ♫
♫ Hand me in, beautiful your life ♫
♫ Come over here, back in your love, in my life ♫
[Oasis]
I introduce Kang Yeo Jin, CEO of Hanil Salon.
Whoa, who do we have here?
Long time no see.
I'll be in your family from now on, too.
What did  you say? Family?
- Who is he?
- Someone helping out with my store.
If I succeed in this deal, will you give me some shares?
But you still shouldn't go out with him.
What kind of bullshit is that!
He's your hyung and friend, but you let him live as a thug?
By the way, I'm trying to start something else, too.
Lee Doo Hak?
Why are you here?
♫ Let me go ♫