[Oasis]
[This drama is fiction. The characters, places, agencies, organizations, incidents, and settings have no relevance to real-life events.]
[Episode 4]
♫ Should auld acquaintance be forgot ♫
♫ And the days of auld lang syne? ♫
Thank you. Have a good time.
♫ And the days of auld lang syne ♫
I introduce to you, the CEO of Paris Salon, Kang Yeo Jin.
Thanks.
You've worked so hard today.
What do you mean, hard work?
More importantly,
this is quite amazing. You did the interior design yourself.
It's like you returned to female college days
when you were bold, smart, and pretty.
Why do you keep flattering me like that!
I'm old now.
I mean it.
You were more beautiful than any of the guests who came today.
You shouldn't say that even if you don't mean it.
But...
how do I repay you for all of this...
You can repay me.
[French Chanson]
Do you know this song?
Why is this LP here?
It's a chanson that I happened to hear once
and ended up liking.
I didn't know that.
I just asked the band for some recommendations for chansons with a nice vibe.
What a coincidence.
It is probably fate.
Or destiny.
I don't even know the meaning of the lyrics yet.
"The life I've lived
was in waiting for you."
That line pierced my heart.
If you keep doing this,
I would be so sorry.
I must have drank too much. I'm getting a bit dizzy...
Are you very dizzy?
No, I think I'll be fine once I rest a bit.
It's quite late now.
My son told me he was coming home today, too.
He will probably be waiting for me.
We should both go home now, Oppa.
Team Captain Oh will take you home.
Are you okay?
Yes.
It's a bit late but congratulations on a successful launch of your business.
It is all thanks to you, Team Captain.
Also,
thank you for the LP.
No problem.
It is a song that the Deputy Director listens to often,
so wouldn't it be even better if he listens to it with you, Ms. Kang?
I'm grateful to you for asking.
Did you listen to it together?
Yes.
Also, please don't ever tell the Deputy Director that I asked you.
Of course not.
Here you go.
It's not much, but it's a sign of my gratitude.
No, thank you.
I would get in trouble by the Deputy Director.
I am giving this to you so that you take good care of the Deputy Director,
so it's all right for you to take it.
Thank you.
You've done a lot today.
Yes, thank you for all sorts of things.
You should hurry inside and rest.
Yes.
Mother.
Why are you coming home so late?
Who is he?
He's someone who helps out with my business.
Son, let's hurry up and go inside.
Your mom is in such a good mood tonight!
Have a drink with your mother, okay?
I also want to have a drink with you,
but I have to go now since I have exams starting tomorrow.
Today was the first time you came home, and you're just going to leave like that?
I will come home often now.
- Really.
- Son...
You know that you're the only one I have now, right?
If an obstacle appears in your way,
I will do everything to clear it, even if it means my body were to break.
So,
you can't disappoint me, either.
You have to take the bar, okay?
Don't worry.
Mom,
I won't ever disappoint you.
I'm also...
thinking of becoming someone with power.
My child, you are so good!
I escorted her safely back to her home.
But I saw that Choi Cheol Woong came home.
He wouldn't have recognized me.
But the thing is...
will it be okay if Ms. Kang finds out later that you were involved
with what happened with Choi Cheol Woong, Deputy Director?
She mustn't know for the rest of her life.
- Home run!
- Home run, home run, home run!
[Completely sold out]
[No Ticket Scalping]
Ahjussi, I've got tickets.
30,000 won per ticket.
What the hell?
It's the bottom of the first inning.
Since the first inning is over, I'll buy it for 25,000 won.
Okay. 27,000 won.
Geez...
- Okay!
- Okay.
Hyung Joo, three tickets for 27,000 won.
Gosh, it's the bottom of the first inning.
Gosh, okay. Okay.
Here.
Have a good time.
- Fighting!
Let's go watch baseball!
Let's go! Give us three tickets!
How much for each ticket?
10,000 won each, so 30,000 won...
Gosh, this bastard!
Hey, are we doing business by digging dirt?
We stayed up all night to buy these tickets! Geez!
We're not selling it to you. Leave us.
How could you do this after promising to give it to us for 10,000 won!
How could I?
I just did, so what?
Go and listen to the radio
while I tell you nicely. Okay?
- I'm sorry.
- Wait.
Take the tickets.
Aigoo.
T-Thank you!
- You should say thank you!
- Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Have fun watching!
The kids say they want to see it.
Are we almost done selling everything?
- There's exactly one ticket left.
- Oh, one ticket.
Can't you just give me that one ticket?
Gosh, what bastard is saying that–
It's me.
Lee Doo Hak, you bastard!
- You scared me, you bastard!
- Hyungnim!
Hyungnims! Seon Woo!
- Doo Hak!
- Gosh, what are you doing scalping tickets?
Gosh, you lost a lot of weight.
No, I gained even more weight.
All right!
I heard the news that you came out of prison when I went to visit you.
I'm sorry.
And you came to see us only now, you bastard?
Come on, today's a good day!
- Hey, drink up.
- Yes.
But...
- did you hear about Young Pil?
- What?
- Hey!
- Gosh, that bastard.
I wonder what he's up to.
The assemblyman who is serving in office for our district
[2 years ago in Gwangju Prison]
is not satisfied with the state punishment given to a bastard who committed promissory note fraud.
Shit.
The sentence that the old man laid down for you is for you to never be able to lift a spoon.
The old man you are serving isn't an assemblyman, but a scumbag and an evil business owner.
F-For me, I don't know that old man at all!
Obviously, you wouldn't know the old man.
But the building in Cheonan that you forged is owned by the old man's sister-in-law.
I-I didn't know. I really didn't know!
I'm sorry!
- Start.
- P-Please don't do this!
Take this.
I can't do it!
I can't do it, either!
This bastard!
It's almost time for a close out roll call, so what's everyone doing here?
Who's that guy?
He's in the same cell as them.
Hey, kid!
You talking to me?
What are you doing, you bastard!
Oh, my!
Everyone, don't move!
Kid, you must not know me well,
but you won't be able to live out your full lifespan now.
And I guess you don't know me very well,
but I have no desire to live out my full lifespan.
If you even leave a scratch on my body,
your body parts will scatter in all different directions.
Really?
Do whatever you want, then.
Either, we both live or we both die.
What's this! What's going on!
Don't move!
Don't move.
Don't move! I'll kill you!
Hey! Your body parts will scatter in all different directions.
Hey, Seon Woo! Do you really want to die?
When did I ever say "I'll kill you"?
- Wasn't it "I'll kill you"?
- Of course not!
Hyungs, you tell him.
Yeah, you should do that cooler!
Cooler?
- Try it again.
- I'll kill you!
You're making fun of me, aren't you!
Doo Hak, you went through a lot because of that bastard, Young Pil.
They say a solitary confinement supposedly changes a person after entering it just once.
You're probably the first person to enter it four times
in the history of the Ministry of Justice.
That's right.
In the solitary confinement,
I realized why they call prison a "school."
You can never learn how f***ed up this world is from books.
That's right.
You've just got one star now, and you're already a professor.
I'm a one star that's more like a five star general.
- Isn't that right?
- Yes, that's right, Hyungnim.
- Right?
- Hey, lift your cups.
To our five star general, cheers!
Cheers!
You've traveled a long way to get here.
Wow...
I wasn't sure when my aunt might change her mind,
so I quickly gathered some of her stuff and came.
Hey, even so, how could you bring unwashed clothes!
Just wash it here and wear it!
Gosh!
♫ It's already in the past. ♫
[Returned to Sender: From Oh Jung Shin to Lee Doo Hak]
♫ Though I keep thinking that to myself and turn back ♫
♫ The sad look in your eyes grow blurry ♫
♫ More than the separation... ♫
What are you guys doing?
You.
Aren't you afraid of me?
I am. But...
you're pretty.
♫ Like the starlight ♫
♫ Above your round eyes ♫
[Certificate of Registration for Sun Film Company]
You know Sun Film Company, right?
It's located in this building.
Drive safely!
Goodbye, Boss!
I think he believes that you're the landlord.
Of course, he should believe it.
Gosh, it's not easy.
What's wrong with you, man!
If so, then what about Seoul and Gyeonggi-do?
The copyright market is about 33% in Seoul with the neighboring areas included.
For Gyeonggi-do and Gangwon-do, it's about 15%.
Gosh...
Geez.
But if you want to enter the Gyeonggi-do and Gangwon-do market,
you should target the central distributor.
Although I would have to put my neck on the line.
Central distributor?
[Winner of College Music Festival, Shin Bo Yeon]
♫ The more I try to forget you ♫
♫ I want to hold your hand ♫
♫ I want to be like a birthday ♫
Let's just have a drink.
- Right now?
- The boss says to sing only in the daytime.
In the evening, the customers don't like it.
♫ I want to look at your mind, hate me or nice ♫
♫ Hand me in, beautiful your life ♫
♫ Come over here, back in your love, in my life ♫
♫ Let me go ♫
Dad...
I'm so pathetic, huh?
I couldn't even protect such a small theater.
♫ In your life ♫
But don't worry.
I will reclaim that theater no matter what!
♫ I want to be myself ♫
I miss you, Dad.
♫ Let me go ♫
And Mom, too.
♫ In my life ♫
♫ Let me go and my life ♫
[Returned to Sender: From Oh Jung Shin to Lee Doo Hak]
♫ Let me go ♫
Hey, Lee Doo Hak!
♫ In your life ♫
Are you doing well, you bastard?
♫ Love you no more ♫
Did you come out of jail yet?
♫ I want to be myself ♫
You probably have.
Then again,
rather than seeing each other live such a pitiful life,
it was good that we broke up.
We did the right thing.
Please let go
of Jung Shin now.
Excuse me?
That girl...
I thought she would
forget you once time passed...
I don't think...
I have much time left to live.
It is my last wish.
Please help me.
Gosh...
Hey, Doo Hak!
Gosh, Doo Hak!
Hey, where have you been all this time?
- Poong Ho hyungnim got caught!
- What?
To which police station?
If it's the police, we could try bribing them, at least.
They took him to Kwang Tak.
I told you those guys are really out to get us after last time,
so you needed to stay by Poong Ho hyungnim at all times!
I'm sorry.
Doo Hak...
they said you should come by yourself.
What do we do?
No, you shouldn't do it!
You would be going to die, Doo Hak!
It's just that Kwang Tak's gang didn't expand their influence yet.
Don't you know that it's already in the top five gangs in Seoul?
I know you're loyal,
but this is just suicide!
Hey, Seon Woo. What do you think?
I mean, I don't care.
I have you, Hyungnim.
Hey, do you know how many guys they have?
And they're not just using their fists.
They're all carrying weapons!
Whether you ambush them or face them head-on,
that... w-who, who was that again?
Yeah, even Bruce Lee would have a hard time coming back alive from that!
It doesn't matter to me.
I would just need to beat up that one guy, Kwang Tak!
Hey! Is this the time to be cleaning right now?
Doo Hak, are you writing the Romance of Three Kingdoms right now?
Will the war be over once you defeat the leader of the other army?
Is the world of gangsters really that clean and neat?
Is it?
Then what do you want me to do?
I can't just leave Poong Ho hyung by himself.
Surrender.
What did you say?
I heard that Yeom Kwang Tak is a pretty loyal guy.
If you really go by yourself to save Poong Ho,
then he may accept your surrender.
After surrendering, then what?
Are you telling him to become one of Kwang Tak's minions
just to save one of our cellmates?
For a guy who should be a high ranking gangster if he were to become one?
Then he shouldn't become a minion.
If I'm not a minion, then what?
Young Pil hyung, that fighter guy... he's here...
What are you saying, you bastard?
Wow, look who it is. It's been a while.
Yoo Young Pil?
Do you remember what I told you in prison?
That you will die before your time.
You bastard. You dare laugh?
Your hyungnim invited me.
So let's just go quietly.
He's here.
Doo Hak!
My name is Lee Doo Hak.
Gosh, you're quite successful, aren't you?
Seeing how you've become the boss of forgers at age 25.
B-B...
Y-You know, you are our b-boss.
What's this? Are you the boss or not?
I-I...
guess I am the boss. Yes...
In any case,
While growing up with Poong Ho hyung in the orphanage, we were like brothers
and shared even a bean together.
Now that he's getting a bit successful with his business, he's completely ignoring me.
What do you think? Since you're the boss, say something.
It's human nature to be okay to
split a bean to share, but not want to split a crate full of beans.
Oh, really?
Gosh, you're so stingy.
Then, you will need to take responsibility as the boss, right?
But I don't want to live being so stingy.
I will split that crate of beans
to share with you.
We will become part of your family.
What did you say? A family?
Hyungnim.
Hey, Seon Woo.
Is this bastard on drugs or something?
So?
Will you accept us as your family?
It's half of the money that our family of four earned from scalping baseball tickets.
The law enforcement has been cracking down hard,
so we're not getting much business.
Doo Hak...
Wow!
You've got guts! He's got what it takes.
Have a drink with me.
Hey.
I heard you're not one to bow your head to anyone.
I heard you refused to bow to Young Pil to the very end in prison.
How come you are trying to bow your head and come under me?
Do you want me to guess what it is?
There's a saying that is popular among kids these days.
"Keep your friends close,
but your enemies closer."
It's easiest for those who are close to stab someone in the back.
That is what you call a coup d'etat, you bastard.
You know what that is, right? A coup d'etat?
Are you trying to bring down my gang?
Tell me.
I'm right, no?
Damn it, you've found out my secret.
You're quite sharp.
Young Pil.
This son of a bitch!
What are you bastards doing! Hurry up and attack him!
What if...
he doesn't accept my surrender?
These are tear gas grenades we picked up last time during a student protest near the baseball stadium.
With this, you should be able to escape.
Seon Woo!
All right. Do you have a towel?
Gosh.
Put that away, you bastard.
You think if you just kill me, everything will be over, right?
My underlings will follow you to the ends of the earth and chew you up.
I won't kill you, Hyungnim.
You won't be able to survive unless you kill me.
So, it would be better for you to just kill me now.
I'll say it again,
but I won't die and I won't kill you, either, Hyungnim.
Then what are you trying to do?
The water's been already spilt.
Even if the water's been spilt,
you can just fill it again as long as the cup isn't broken.
Hey, Hyungnim.
Hurry up and sit down.
Gosh, geez.
Hyungnim, you're not broken yet.
We'll become your water.
Cut the crap, you asshole.
We mean it.
If you would accept us,
we will give you half of our earnings from forgery.
What kind of game are you playing with me right now?
I know you have great ambitions.
You're not one to be satisfied with just Mugyo-dong.
If you want to take over Myeong-dong and Seoul,
you would need a fighter like me,
and I would need a lord and an organization like you and your gang, Hyungnim.
So what you're saying is that I am Liu Bei
and that you're something like Zhao Yun?
Think of it however you'd like.
All right. But...
how do I trust that you won't stab me in the back?
Don't you think I'd need
something as a collateral?
If you hold something as a collateral, that's a business transaction,
and we can't become a family.
You will be suspicious of me, no matter what I give you.
All right.
We will look for someone else.
Go back home safely.
Oath of Brotherhood...
let's do it.
Let's be a family, you bastard.
Give me a cigarette.
All right, so have you done some studying?
Boss, you want to earn more money, right?
But there's a bit of a limit to your profits as an entertainment promoter in Gwangju and Jeonnam,
- which is only 10% of the market.
- Your introduction is way too long.
We should...
enter the Gyeonggi-do market.
What?
Just two or three years ago,
Gyeonggi-do and Gangwon-do together only made up 15% of the market,
but with the growth of satellite cities around the capital,
the market has grown much larger.
It means there is potential.
What in the world are you talking about?
Do you know what kind of a business this is?
If you try to take over someone else's territory, you'll end up in big trouble!
You might get stabbed!
Gyeonggi-do and Gangwon-do are already being split among three distributors.
So how would we force our way into the market?
We would break that triangular formation and bring one of them down,
and then take its place.
- How?
- We'll have to figure out a way.
But if I manage to pull this off,
can you give me company shares?
Gosh, this girl's like a sly fox!
All right, go for it then.
If you manage to succeed, I won't only give you shares
but I will even marry you.
You mean that, right?
You have to keep this promise, okay?
This girl already has something in mind, huh?
All right. Go ahead and try.
Wait— P-President Cha!
How much shares does Kwang Tak hyungnim own again?
30% on management, with no invested capital.
30%?
He's such a thief.
If you live on spending your own money,
then you're not a real gangster!
But those punks did some shitty bookkeeping.
Not to mention the sales, even.
Young Pil seems to be pocketing some money by creating
a false ledger with the liquor wholesaler he looks after.
I see.
I really can't understand what the boss was  thinking
when he decided to take him in.
Hey, let's say we can take him in to boost our fighting power.
But how can he be in the same ranks as our hyungnim?
Don't you agree, Hyungnim?
These punks, seriously.
You're ruining appetite.
- I'm sorry!
- I'm sorry, Hyungnim.
Is this a soup and rice shop?
Aigoo, of course, there wouldn't be any customers at this luxurious hotel
since it reeks of soup and radish kimchi.
I know he entrusted this place to you.
But I need to have lunch and coffee here to have good digestion.
I'll buy you digestive medicine if you've got digestion problems.
So order from the existing menu from now on.
Make sure to pay, though.
This little punk...
Have some coffee before you go.
It's my treat today.
We're family, right?
Family, my foot.
I don't consider you to be my family.
Watch out.
Let's get along, okay?
I'll do my best!
- Let's go.
- How ridiculous.
Yes, President Yoon.
Me? I'm working.
For what business?
What did you say?
Gosh, why do you keep asking for my guys for such embarrassing things?
What did you  say? Okay.
Aigoo. Make sure you treat my guys, then.
Yes, yes. Oh, and also...
you know, after the shooting, the actress...
That's right.
Yes, yes. No, just naturally invite her to drink. All right?
Rotary club and all full amenity.
This is a gift from Hyungnim.
Let me know if there's anything you need.
Thank you, Hyungnim!
I'll make this short.
From now on, there's no such thing as one taking or eating more than the other.
A family eats, poops, and fights together. Understood?
Yes, Hyungnim!
Raise your glasses.
- Cheers.
- Cheers!
My, my.
Okay, okay.
Aigoo, shit.
Yes.
Hey, where's Doo Hak?
Aigoo!
Gosh!
Got it.
Manager, I heard the shooting was delayed a lot.
Will we be able to finish by the premiere date?
I won't let those bastards go.
I'll take care of it myself, so Namdo Film Studio stay out of this. Okay?
Gosh, Manager!
Where are you going?
Gosh.
- Open the criminals mouth and feed her the poison!
- Yes, sir!
Your Highness!
No, Your Highness!
Is the poison she ate a real poison?
It's an herbal tea.
Oh, an herbal tea.
Gosh, I'm so glad.
- No!
- Your Highness!
Your Highness!
- By the way...
That court lady seems to be wearing a watch.
Awesome.
Cut!
Gosh... hey!
- What's going on now?
- What's that? Oh, my. Wait.
Whoa! What the heck?
Director!
Wait, help me get back up.
Gosh. What the heck is this? Is it no good?
Bravo!
Song Yeon Ju, a male director wanted by the 21st century so badly
is waiting for you right now.
Please hurry up and come out.
He seems to be from the other movie Song Yeon Ju is a part of.
Hey! Tell him to keep waiting!
We also need to finish this scene today, okay?
Hey, everyone, gather!
If you don't move out in three seconds,
- we won't hold back anymore.
- N-No one told you to hold back!
One!
Two!
- Go.
- Wh-Whoa—
- Move!
- W-Wait—
What's this?
- Aigoo.
- Gosh, no!
- Let go!
- Huh?
- Oh, my gosh!
You want to die?
- Sit down.
- You almost had me there!
- Sit down!
- Come on.
Aigoo! You can't!
Let go. Let go of me!
You assholes!
Seriously.
Gosh, this little!
Hey.
Escort her politely.
- Mind your manners.
- I'm sorry.
Not to me. Okay?
I'm sorry.
Hey, forget it. Let's go.
Yes, Hyungnim.
- We're done here.
- Please come this way.
Who dares to intrude a sacred filming set—
You can't take her like that! We need to finish this scene!
- You can't!
- You can't do this!
J-Jung—
No, you can't—
Lee Doo Hak?
Long time no see.
Why are you here?
Jung Shin, what are you doing? Hurry up and move aside.
Leave.
I'm sorry to interrupt, Hyungnim.
We need to bring Song Yeon Ju quickly.
They insisted the daytime scene must be filmed today.
Are you a thug?
A thug?
- Excuse me, lady. You talk a little too nicely.
- Seon Woo.
You can stay out of this.
I said, are you a thug?
Yes.
You avoided my visits merely to live like this?
I never avoided them.
I ended up in jail because of you.
If it were you, would you want to see you?
You really...
- Do you really think I was to blame?
- Also...
I'm doing my best in life in my own way.
A thief who's diligently stealing is doing his best as well then, huh?
A petty thief who stole a wallet gets scorned,
but a big thief who stole a country
is feared by the world.
You really lost your mind, huh?
That's not it.
The one you used to know had lost his mind.
Having ridiculous thoughts such as thinking you'll be blessed if you're loyal to your parents,
study hard, and be patriotic to your country.
In this twisted world,
living in a twisted way is the correct way.
Whoa...
Lee Doo Hak, you really...
became a complete trash.
Trash?
Sure.
The noble daughter of a theater-running family...
should never encounter this trash again.
- Hey, let's withdraw!
- Yes, Hyungnim.
You should drink more slowly.
You somehow knew where I was, huh?
Did you get used to Seoul yet?
Is something wrong?
You...
keep in touch with Doo Hak, right?
Yes.
Since he's my hyung and friend.
He's your hyung and friend,
but you let him live as a thug?
You met him?
Yes.
I met him when...
he barged into our filming set to snatch out an actress.
It must be great to be you!
You have a thug as a friend.
We're not at young ages anymore.
Who would listen to who? We just...
live according to our fates.
Fates.
Fates?
Are people who used to be servants of your place all fated to be thugs?
Are all ex-convicts fated to live as thugs?
Even if the entire world points its fingers at him, at least...
you shouldn't be doing the same, you asshole!
There's no such thing as fate in this world.
Lee Doo Hak, you really...
became a complete trash.
Aigoo. Are you okay?
I told you to drink in moderation.
Cheol Woong...
I have a request.
Please bring...
Doo Hak out of that place.
Don't let him live as a thug, please?
You're really the only one.
If you let him live like that...
it's too unfortunate for Doo Hak.
It's too unfortunate for our poor Doo Hak.
Jung Shin...
can't you...
forget about him now?
Cheol Woong...
I have something to ask you.
Please tell me honestly.
Go ahead.
Did...
Doo Hak really kill a person?
No matter how I think about it, he's not the type to do such thing.
He did.
Doo Hak hyung was the one.
He was avenging me on the guy who beat me up.
But there was an accident.
What a twisted life that asshole has.
Isn't this really too harsh?
Aren't you being too harsh on that poor kid?
Gosh, I'm about to die, seriously.
Whoa, just how much did you drink?
It still reeks of alcohol!
What's that? Is it hangover soup?
Gosh, Yang Ja, you're the best.
Gosh, the heartburn.
My heart burns more, you wench.
You even have a knight who brings your drunken ass home, huh?
Who did?
Don't you remember?
Cheol Woong brought you all the way home.
Cheol Woong did?
Did you really black out or are you pretending?
That can't be, though.
I haven't seen him since high school.
But he became really handsome.
By the way, since when have you two been talking?
Wait, more importantly— Where did it go?
What time is it right now?
Whoa! I'm late, late. So late!
- Hey, I prepared the meal! Eat it before you go!
- I don't have the time!
But seriously, what's up with your hair?
Are you a ball of iron?
My hair just doesn't grow. What can I do?
Who is he?
He's my guest.
Wait, so...
did you come to advise me to stop being a thug?
Nope.
What right do I have? I'm also a trash.
It seems...
Jung Shin still isn't over you, Hyung.
She cried a lot.
She must've pitied me.
I don't think that was all.
When you were in prison, it seems she wrote letters constantly
and went to visit you frequently, too.
Why did you break up?
It was just too nasty.
So I broke up with her.
Let's stop talking about this.
Talking about young love and memories, it's childish.
Hyung...
do I have to become a prosecutor?
Yes.
Before you graduate.
In that case...
since I'm granting your wish...
you grant my wish, too.
I can...
go out with Jung Shin now, right?
Hey, Cheol Woong...
there's nothing between Jung Shin and I anymore.
You mean it, right?
You mean what you just said, right?
However...
you still shouldn't go out with her.
She's a stranger to you, so for what reason?
You said in your own words earlier...
that you're also a trash.
At least for old times' sakes,
Jung Shin shouldn't go out with trash like us.
Isn't that so?
You're the one who made become a trash.
What did you say?
Don't think you're the only victim, Hyung.
I haven't felt at peace even for a single day, ever since that day.
That's why...
I'm telling you to leave Jung Shin alone.
Are you going to go to Jung Shin and tell her?
That I'm actually the murderer?
If that's not the case, then why?
Why on Earth can't I?
Jung Shin looking at me,
who has become a thug, with disgust by your side...
It annoys me just thinking about it.
You think you always yielded for me, huh?
Don't be mistaken.
Hyung, you have never really considered me your friend or dongsaeng.
Since you can no longer gain Jung Shin's heart,
you're telling me not to date her, either?
What kind of bullshit is that!
You and I are both shitty people.
Shitty people should talk bullshit.
Would we be talking like decent people?
[Joongbu Film Distribution Company]
Go and target Joongbu Film Distribution Company.
President Na there is famous for gambling.
I'm not sure if he got involved with commissioned card sharks,
but he's rumored to be quite low on cash lately.
[Namdo Film Studio]
Oh, you work for President Cha?
Yes.
Well, I do know President Cha well.
Anyhow, what's brings you?
President Cha wants to partner up with you, President Na.
She wants me to join in on distributions in Jeolla-do?
No, she wants to do distributions in Gyeonggang with you.
What?
Whoa...
Now, now. I complimented her as a heroine,
but President Cha got a lot of gall, huh?
You can continue the management as you've been doing.
President Cha just wants about 30% of the shares.
Hey, now.
People in this field are more territorial than thugs.
If you recklessly enter someone else's region, you'll be ousted.
Go and tell her, okay?
If she wants to live a long life,
she should just keep playing house in Gwangju.
Understood.
Right.
You must've borrowed a lot of money on the house.
In fact, President Cha doesn't know about your gambling.
That's why I was going to oppose her proposal.
But I didn't want to soil her relationship with you, so I just dropped by.
Thank you so much for rejecting.
Wait!
30% of the shares?
How much was she going to pay per share?
So?
- I called 100 million won.
- What—
It's a little too much.
If you think about the market that will grow, it's nothing.
By the way,
President Na had conditions, right?
- First off, he asked for complete confidentiality.
- Of course.
If word gets out, he won't be able to keep doing business in Gyeonggang.
And then?
He asked for the shares to be returned whenever he pays you back.
What did you say?
What's good for us, then?
If he just pays back the principal, we can't even get the interest!
President Cha, this is such a losing deal!
And so?
I said okay.
Have you gone mad?
My goodness.
You did so well.
- President Cha!
- It's going to take more than eternity for you to get on her level.
Have you ever heard a gambler cleared his debt?
Okay, then. What about a gambler getting more debt?
That's it, all right? That's exactly it.
It contains about three large ones.
So go and get Joongbu in your hands.
Oh, my!
You said you'll give me my shares, right?
How many shares will you give?
Do you not trust me?
Do you trust me, President Cha?
Okay.
What is it that you want?
If I reach 50% distribution in Gyeonggang region after obtaining Joobgbu,
give me 30% of the shares.
Whoa, whoa. Has this girl gone mad?
Did you really hurt your head or something?
What if you fail?
I'll have to spend the rest of my life as your servant, then.
I'll need to think about this.
What do you mean a spy?
We call them informants,
but regular people call them spies.
Are you saying Cheol Woong really did such a dangerous work?
Who exactly order my son to do such thing?
Not sure.
For now, it's reported he volunteered after early discharge.
Nowadays, things changed a lot,
so we don't even force it, not that it's possible.
But how did he get found out?
The student union's students caught on to Cheol Woong's suspicious activities
and must've questioned him at their school.
But...
Cheol Woong had a good friend.
Was Lee Doo Hak his name?
I heard he barged in alone against the students and saved Cheol Woong.
Cheol Woong won't be able to be a student activist anymore.
If he just quietly studies for the civil exam, there won't be any problems.
Quietly.
[One Year Later]
Good job, Doo Hak.
The sales are consistent and
most of all, it's great there aren't any small troubles.
Thank you, Hyungnim.
The shareholders have  a lot of complaint.
You'll need to work harder, Young Pil.
- I'm sorry, Hyungnim.
- Also...
do you still order and eat soup and rice at the hotel's coffee shop?
Sorry?
Just open a soup and rice place somewhere.
Should I open one up for you?
Let's give some more thoughts into our lives, Young Pil.
Hyungnim.
What do you think about me taking and managing Young Pil's hotel and night club?
Hey, you asshole! Do you really want to die?
- Hey, Young Pil, that's not what I meant—
- Shut up!
- I'll really rip your mouth—
- You rude bastard.
Get out, you punk.
Get out.
Gosh, seriously.
You, too.
You shouldn't say such things.
If you take over Young Pil's turf, what will his family live on?
Hyungnim...
that's not what I meant.
I was going to entrust my hotel and night club to Young Pil.
What did you say?
Since my turf's system is stable,
Young Pil wouldn't find it difficult to manage it.
If I take over Young Pil's turf and improve it,
I thought it'd stabilized both sides.
Wait, then...
you were saying you wanted to switch turfs with him?
Yes, that's right.
My goodness, that asshole needs to listen to the end.
We're one family, aren't we, Hyungnim?
Aigoo.
[Appointment Ceremony for Judicial Trainees]
Cheol Woong!
Jung Shin.
Congratulations, Sir.
- Thank you.
- Great job.
Cheol Woong!
Mother!
Your mother no longer has any wishes in this life.
Don't cry now. It's a good day.
I'm getting carried away.
Your father...
should've seen this site.
I'll go see father soon to his grave.
It's been too long since I went.
You should.
Thankfully...
the uncle here is...
taking  a good care of father's grave.
I'm always thankful to you, Uncle.
Not at all. It's a matter of course.
I'm so proud of you.
I'm really proud.
You're...
making the Choi family great again.
Well, this is all thanks to you, Uncle.
What did I ever do to help?
Wait, why are you crying, Aunt?
Y-You...
You did really well.
Why don't you both spend a night at our house today?
Let me pour you a glass.
Whoa...
No, not at all. We need to hurry back.
We have farming work piled up.
Don't even mention it.
This man is farming on a strip of land in Seoul.
Gosh.
I can afford to stay a night.
This woman, seriously.
You have tons of work to do!
Aigoo, you're same as ever, Uncle.
Cheol Woong, don't mind us.
- I'll be going ahead, okay?
- Okay.
- In that case, I'll come and visit you soon.
- Sure.
You did well.
Please take care.
Why? Are you expecting someone?
Huh?
It's nothing at all.
Congrats. For him to pass the civil exam so soon...
who does he take after to be smart?
Is it the mom or the dad?
We'll need to say it's the mom.
All right.
While we're on the topic, Oppa,
I have a request.
Sure, a request from you. What is it?
Cheol Woong wants to be a prosecutor.
Please help him.
His bar exam score was it the top rankings.
However, according to Minister of Justice's wife who comes to our store,
it's impossible to be a judge or prosecutor if you have a history of being a student activist.
Yes.
Cheol Woong will need to be an attorney. I can't help with that, either.
It's obvious there  will be more controversy if we say he was actually an informant of a government agency.
Isn't that actually the reason they should let him be a prosecutor?
He sealed his mouth shut and worked for the country.
It's not that easy.
When I looked at the records,
he never provided any solid info on the student union's members.
He made it through by walking on the tightrope.
He's neither black or white, but grey.
He wishes to become a prosecutor.
And my wish is the same.
If he had cooperated with the agency, we could've said he's an elite prosecutor.
But the world isn't easy.
Although his smart like his mother,
his stubborn way of living to protect his cheap conscience takes after his father.
That's true.
He takes after his father.
Cheol Woong is...
just like his biological father,
so he has ambitions.
He desires to have power.
Whoa.
You need to at least say hi if you're here.
How can you just leave?
Good job.
Go let out some stress.
What's this?
Oh, my.
Lee Doo Hak's become so lavish after becoming Gwang Tak gang's number two, huh?
How cool.
Anyway...
I've completed your order at this point, right?
Don't be arrogant.
You finally got the qualifications to pay me back. This is the beginning.
That's right. It's the beginning.
By the way...
I'm trying to start something else, too.
I'm going to...
make Jung Shin my woman.
Of course.
He is also a foolish father,
who still doesn't recognize his son,
who is right in front of his eyes.
Please...
help Cheol Woong become a prosecutor...
as his father.
Stop acting wicked.
I fully know you haven't gotten over Jung Shin yet.
If you want, Hyung, let's compete again like we did in high school.
It'll be a fair play.
Okay?
Why you little!
♫ Will I be able to come to you again? ♫
♫ Trembling eyes, they're even more sorrowful ♫
♫ Above the rough sky, my heart floats away ♫
♫ Only your name ♫
[Oasis]
Don't you have any other sound reasons?
Doo Hak hyung is okay, but not me?
I'm not afraid.
Why? Because I did it to live like a human being!
Just hit me like you always did.
President Cha!
You're the best, President Cha.
I'm not the puppet you used to know.
I'm Korea's prosecutor, Choi Cheol Woong.
I just can't understand why you're showing me so much mercy.
Jung Shin...
Jung Shin has been kidnapped, I said.
If you help me, I think there might be a way.
♫ The times I confronted ♫